gtf.net.au 2012-03-17

# Green Tree Frog Internet Provider

## Your Privacy

This privacy policy and collection statement applies to the www.greentreefrog.net.au website and sets out the information handling policies of Green Tree Frog ABN 75 132 229 399\. By accessing this website you agree to the terms of this privacy policy and collection statement.

Green tree frog has adopted this privacy policy to demonstrate its commitment to handling personal information about individuals responsibly and in compliance with legal requirements of privacy protection.

We comply with the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988.

### What personal information we collect

We only collect personal information from you if it is relevant to our relationship with you and necessary to provide our services. Various pages on this website invite you to provide personal information. When you register your interest or purchase products on-line, the personal information we collect includes your name, billing and delivery addresses, delivery instructions, credit card details, email address, contact phone numbers, address, confirmation that you are over 18, details of your operating system and some statistical information about your household. If you are an Green tree frog customer, we may ask you for your user name, password, driver's license number, date of birth and mother's maiden name for the purpose of identifying you over the telephone. We also hold details of the services we provide to our customers, such as usage details.

If you choose not to provide us with personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the services you require.

### How we collect personal information

We only collect personal information directly from you on-line or on the phone. We only collect personal information by lawful and fair means and not in an unreasonably intrusive way. We do not collect any 'sensitive information', such as information relating to your race, political opinions, membership of a political association or trade association, religious beliefs or sexual preferences.

When we collect personal information we take steps to ensure that you are made aware of what information we are collecting, how that information is used and to whom it is disclosed. We do this by displaying a link to this privacy policy and collection statement wherever we collect information.

### We do not collect information from children

To sign up to an Green tree frog contract and select a plan, you must be at least 18 years old. In all other cases, for example if you use the Contact Us form, no information may be submitted to us by persons under the age of 13 without the consent of a parent or legal guardian.

### How we use personal information

We only use your personal information for the purpose for which we collected it in the first place - that is to provide you with our goods and services. We do not use your information for direct marketing purposes. We limit our use and disclosure of your personal information to those uses which are necessary to provide our services to you.

### We do not share your personal information

We do not share, sell or trade personal information to anyone else. In some circumstances it may be necessary to disclose your information to our third party service providers, such as a call centre provider. In all cases, we ensure that your information is secure and that you are afforded the same level of privacy protection.

### Your personal information is secure

There are always risks with providing personal information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet. No technology is completely safe, tamper-proof or hacker-proof. However, we take considerable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. We use up-to-date techniques and processes, which are consistent with current industry standards to keep your personal information secure and confidential.

### Your credit card details

All your credit card information is transmitted to our secure server through a multi-layered encryption mechanism so that no-one can intercept or tamper with your information as it passes over the Internet. We frequently review and update our security systems to ensure that your credit card details are afforded among the best standards of protection available.

### Identifying yourself over the phone

So we can ensure that you are who you say you are, if you contact us by phone, we will ask you to provide identifying information such as your user name, password, mother's maiden name and driver's licence number. If you are unable to provide this information, we may not be able to provide the service you require.

### Cookies

From time to time information may be placed on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is commonly known as a "cookie" and contains information such as your Internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, browser type and traffic patterns. This information does not include any personal identifying information. Cookies show us how and when visitors use our website. The use of cookies is industry standard and many websites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this website.

In most cases this website uses session cookies, which are used during a browser session and expire when you quit your browser. When you close your browser, the session cookie is destroyed and no personal information is kept which might identify should you visit this website at a later date.

If you do not wish to receive cookies or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may not be able to access some parts of our website. Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.x users can disable their cookie settings by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", selecting the "Privacy" tab and changing the privacy settings to "Block All Cookies".

### Email and spam

Our service is an Internet based service and, as such, we endeavour to ensure that all communications are by Internet. The service we provide our clients includes on-line access to usage details and accounts. Where possible, we only contact our customers by email. The information we send our customers sometimes includes information about other services we provide. If we send information of this type to you, we provide you with the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive this information in the future.

### Help us to ensure we hold accurate information

We take reasonable precautions to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, the accuracy of that information depends to a large extent on you. We recommend that you let us know if there are any errors in your personal Information and keep us up-to-date with changes to personal information such as your name or address.

### Your rights

You have a right to access your personal information. This is subject to some exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to access your personal information you can make a request by emailing us at privacy@Green tree frog .com.au. This service is free unless the personal information you request requires significant preparation time. Before we act on requests of this nature, we will tell you how much this service will cost. We will respond within 30 days.

### What to do if you think we have made a mistake

We are committed to the protection of your privacy and our policies, processes and systems have been developed with this intent. However, errors do occur sometimes. If you think we have not lived up to our commitment, we invite you to contact us.

Our objective is to respond to any complaint within 7 days. Where we have not met our privacy commitments, we will apologise and take reasonable action to correct the practice or omission which led to the error. If we cannot resolve your concern to your satisfaction, you can refer the matter to the Privacy Commissioner on 1800 023 985.

### How to contact us

For more information about our commitment to protecting your privacy, please contact us at:  
privacy@greentreefrog.com.au   
Phone 1300 854 820  
Facsimile 1300 854 830   
PO Box 3036 Redfern NSW 2016
